Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files F-J, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Amsterdam News photograph archive, 1920-2012.
8084
New York Amsterdam News.
189 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Photographs, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes photographs and related materials covering a broad range of topics, with a particular focus on day-to-day life in New York's African-American community during the 20th century.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Founded in 1909 by James H. Anderson, the New York Amsterdam News is one of the oldest African-American owned and run newspapers in the country. Initially focused on local news in New York in general and Harlem in particular, the Amsterdam News broadened its scope to include national news under the guidance of editor Dr. C.B. Powell in the 1930s. By the 1960s, the newspaper had become a major voice in the national African-American community, offering extensive coverage of the civil rights movement. Beginning in 1982, the newspaper was edited by Wilbert A. Tatum, under whose guidance the newspaper remained a voice in local and national affairs. In 1996, Tatum turned control of the newspaper over to his daughter, Elinor Tatum, who remained the publisher and editor-in-chief through the 2000s.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes photographs and related materials covering a broad range of topics, with a particular focus on day-to-day life in New York's African-American community during the 20th century. Subjects include civil rights marches and protests, church events, high school graduations, local politics, and fashion. Some photographs were taken by staff photographers, while others originated with wire services or as submissions from individuals or agencies. Formats in the collection include silver gelatin prints, negatives (including many unpublished images), contact sheets, Polaroids, wire photos, and halftone prints. As the working photo archive of a continuously-published newspaper, many of the images have retouching, attached captions, press releases, cover letters, and printer's instructions. In addition to photographs, the collection includes ephemera and manuscript material, including newspaper article drafts, typescript and mimeographed speeches, correspondence, event programs, magazine and newspaper clippings, employment applications, press releases, and newspaper production materials.
The bulk of the materials in the archive range from the mid-1940s through the mid-1990s. The materials are divided into series, reflecting the organization of the materials in the AM News offices. A major sub-series of the collection is the archive of Mel Tapley, who began working for the Amsterdam News in 1942 and served as entertainment editor until his retirement in 1997. The Mel Tapley archive includes a wide variety of material, including correspondence, manuscript and typescript articles and notes, artwork, press kits, publicity photos, and printing plates for comic strips drawn by Tapley.
Photographers represented in the collection include Bert Andrews, Kwame Brathwaite, Al Burley, James C. Campbell, Curt Clemons, Juanita M. Cole, Karl Crutchfield, L. St. Clair Dummett, Monroe S. Frederick II, James Gilbert, Dave Greene, Austin Hansen, Tex Harris, Bob Head, Cecil Layne, David McAdams, Bill Moore, Allen Morgan, Vondel Nichols, Lem Peterkin, George M. West, and Lloyd Yearwood. Photo agencies and services represented include Pictorial Enterprise, Wide World Photo, Harris Photo, News Voice International, Rapid News Photo, United Press International, Negro Press Photo Service, Wagner International Photos, and Ace Creative Photos.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York Amsterdam News.
Titles:
New York Amsterdam news.
Subjects:
African American newspapers.; African Americans -- New York (State) -- New York.
Places:
New York (N.Y.); Harlem (New York, N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Because of the size of this collection, the guide is broken up into several different pages. Each page is then further separated into different series. The majority of the sereis titles come from titles given by the Amsterdam News.
Main Guide Content Listing
Series A. Main photo sequence
The main alphabetic sequence of prints containing material from 1920-2012 with the bulk being 1944-1996.
Subject files A
Subject files B
Subject files C
Subject files D
Subject files E
Subject files F
Subject files G
Subject files H
Subject files I
Subject files J
Subject files K
Subject files L
Subject files M
Subject files N
Subject files O
Subject files P
Subject files Q
Subject files R
Subject files S
Subject files T
Subject files U
Subject files V
Subject files W
Subject files X
Subject files Y
Subject files Z
Series B. Inactive File
File of inactive, defunct, or deceased individuals and organizations. Bulk material dates from before 1980.
Series C. Presorted Photos
A roughly sorted series of photos.
Series D. Semi Alphabetized Photos
A second roughly sorted series of photos. Most date from 1980-1999.
Series E. Dated Folders
Photos from the 1990s sorted by date.
Series F. Sports Photos
Mostly promotional photos from sports teams.
Series G. Contemporary File
An alphabetic sequence of photos primarily from 1988-2000, but with some older material.
Series H. Transfer File
An alphabetic sequence of topical files with bulk material dates from the 1960s-1970s.
Series I. Dead Photo File
Photos from the 2000s organized by date of their publication in the Amsterdam News.
Series J. Loose Unsorted Items
Unsorted items found in various locations around the Amsterdam News office.
Series MT. Mel Tapley Collection
The personal archive of Mel Tapley, who began working at the Amsterdam News in 1942 and served as the entertainment editor until 1997. Includes a wide variety of ephemera, artwork, manuscript and typescript material, and correspondence.
Miscellaneous Mailings and Press Files
Mel Tapley Artwork
Unsorted Photos
Press Mailings
Books and Booklets
Press Kits
Press Releases
Oversize and Fax Press Releases
Periodicals, Newspapers, Magazines
Audio and Visual Media
CONTAINER LIST
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files F
    - F (Box A-39, Folder 238)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Karl Crutchfield, Hens Boyd
      Number of Prints: 9
    - F (Box A-39, Folder 239)
      Subjects include C. Virginia Fields, Fernando Ferrer, Fab 5 Freddy. 2 sets of 2 prints stapled together.
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Fisk University, James Gilbert, Lem Peterkin, Kwame Brathwaite, Carol Rosegg, Ed Krieger, Oluwaseye Olusa
      Number of Prints: 30
    - F (Box A-39, Folder 240)
      Also 2 color slides. 1 Polaroid (integral.) Subjects include Funkmaster Flex, David Dinkins, Aretha Franklin
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Ben Watts, John Harrington, James Gilbert, Wagner International
      Number of Prints: 21
    - Faberware (Box A-40, Folder 1)
      Number of Prints: 2
    - Fabian (Box A-40, Folder 2)
      Number of Prints: 1
    - Fabre, Edwin George (Box A-40, Folder 3)
      Photographer if identified: David McAdams, Freeman Ramsey Jr.
    - Fabrik, Tina (Box A-40, Folder 4)
    - Fabulous Four (Box A-40, Folder 5)
      One single-leaf press release attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Leland Bertrand
    - Fabulous Independents (Box A-40, Folder 6)
    - Facey, Stan (Box A-40, Folder 7)
      One single-leaf press release adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Rothschild
    - Facilities Development Corp. (Box A-40, Folder 8)
    - Factor, John (Box A-40, Folder 9)
    - Faddis, Jon (Box A-40, Folder 10)
      Photographer if identified: Marco Glaviano
    - Fagan, Allan (Box A-40, Folder 11)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene Photo
    - Fagan, Garth (Box A-40, Folder 12)
      One print has single-leaf press release adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Anne Lennox, Gannett Rochester Newspapers
    - Fagan, Scott (Box A-40, Folder 13)
    - Fahs, Raymond (Box A-40, Folder 14)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Faide, Samuel M. (Box A-40, Folder 15)
      Mounted on cardstock.
    - Fair, C. Q. (Dr.) (Box A-40, Folder 16)
    - Fair, James (Box A-40, Folder 17)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Bro. David McAdams Photo
    - Fair, Louis Jr. (Box A-40, Folder 18)
      Also three negatives and one paper stereotype matrix.
      Photographer if identified: Dummett, Geo. W. Smith, J. J. Adams, W. Smith, James C. Campbell,
      Number of Prints: 12
    - Fair, Ronald L. (Box A-40, Folder 19)
      One typescript leaf from publisher attached with a paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Jim Theologos
    - Fair, Willard T. (Box A-40, Folder 20)
    - Fair, Yvonne (Box A-40, Folder 21)
    - Fairbain, Ann (Box A-40, Folder 22)
      One print has typescript leaf from NAACP adhered on verso.
    - Fairbanks, Douglas (Jr.) (Box A-40, Folder 23)
    - Fairbanks, Ronald (Box A-40, Folder 24)
    - Fairfax, Hackley (Box A-40, Folder 25)
    - Fairley, Richard L. (Box A-40, Folder 26)
      Photographer if identified: Largemoor Studios
    - Faison, Carol (Box A-40, Folder 27)
      Photographer if identified: James E. Jackson
    - Faison, Earl (Box A-40, Folder 28)
    - Faison, Ellen (Box A-40, Folder 29)
      Two prints have single typescript leaves attached on verso with staples in all four corners. Note on folder: "Also see 'Round Trip'." Additional print filed under "Ellen Fasion."
      Number of Prints: 4
    - Faison, Frankie (Box A-40, Folder 30)
      Photographer if identified: Friedman-Abeles
    - Faison, George (Box A-40, Folder 31)
      Also one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Si Chi Ko
      Number of Prints: 13
    - Faison, Keibu (Box A-40, Folder 32)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise
    - Faison, Shirley (Box A-40, Folder 33)
    - Faison, Willie (Box A-40, Folder 34)
    - Fait, George (Box A-40, Folder 35)
    - Faith, Hope and Charity (Box A-40, Folder 36)
      Two prints have single-leaf press releases adhered on verso; also one single-leaf press release from RCA News.
      Number of Prints: 5
    - Falana, Lola (Box A-40, Folder 37)
      One print has newspaper clipping adhered on recto; two have single-leaf press releases adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Erni Marshall
      Number of Prints: 18
    - Falconer, John (Dr.) (Box A-40, Folder 38)
      Single typescript leaf with name adhered on verso.
    - Falcons (Box A-40, Folder 39)
      One velox print.
    - Falkener, Ernestine (Box A-40, Folder 40)
    - Falkener, Waldo (Box A-40, Folder 41)
    - Fallis, Melvin C. (Box A-40, Folder 42)
      Single carbonscript leaf from Coca-Cola Company Foods Division attached with paperclip.
    - Falls, Arthur G. (Box A-40, Folder 43)
      Single manuscript leaf adhered on verso.
    - Falls, Vincent (Box A-40, Folder 44)
      Also one laserjet printed photograph.
      Number of Prints: 3
    - Fame, Herb (Box A-40, Folder 45)
      Photographer if identified: Agee, Stevens & AcreeInc.
    - "Families" (Box A-40, Folder 46)
      One photo has staple in corner.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert
    - Family (Box A-40, Folder 47)
      One print with typescript letter from Amsterdam News attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Arnold Krockman, Gerry Goodstein
      Number of Prints: 17
    - "Fame" Family (Box A-40, Folder 48)
      Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons
    - Family Dynamics (Box A-40, Folder 49)
    - Family Stand (Box A-40, Folder 50)
    - Famous Amos (Box A-40, Folder 51)
    - Famous Amos (Box A-40, Folder 52)
      One print has two typescript leaves (press release) attached.
    - Fancher, Charles B. Dr. (Box A-40, Folder 53)
      Photographer if identified: Joe Zinn
    - Fancher, Kirk D. (Box A-40, Folder 54)
    - Fania All-Stars (Box A-40, Folder 55)
    - Fann, Al (Box A-40, Folder 56)
      Also one velox print. One print has three photocopied leaves attached with a paperclip; two single typescripts leaves.
      Photographer if identified: Ed Bailey Photo, Patrick Owens, Monroe S. Frederick II, Harris Photo, Bob Lichtman,
      Number of Prints: 26
    - Fann, Al Jr. (Box A-40, Folder 57)
      Single typescript leaf resume adhered on verso.
    - Fann, Barbara (Box A-40, Folder 58)
      One print has single typescript leaf resume on verso. Three leaf typescript letter to Amsterdam News.
    - Fann, Shelley (Box A-40, Folder 59)
      Single typescript leaf resume adhered on verso. Also one velox print.
    - Fannie Moore Memorial Awards (6th Annal) (Box A-40, Folder 60)
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfieldgraphy
    - Fanning, Mack Jr. (Box A-40, Folder 61)
    - Fant, Crystal (Box A-40, Folder 62)
    - Fant, Ora (Box A-40, Folder 63)
      Photographer if identified: John Lane Studio
    - Fantabulous (Box A-40, Folder 64)
    - Fantastic Four (Box A-40, Folder 65)
    - Fantasy Toys (Box A-40, Folder 66)
    - Far, Yvonne (Box A-40, Folder 67)
    - Farabee, James (Box A-40, Folder 68)
    - Farber, Barry (Box A-40, Folder 69)
    - Farber, Carol (Box A-40, Folder 70)
      One photocopy of a print.
    - Fargas, Antonio (Box A-40, Folder 71)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Glen Frieson
    - Fargas, Antonio (Box A-40, Folder 72)
    - Farkas, Alexander (Box A-40, Folder 73)
      Also one newspaper clipping.
    - Farkas, George (Box A-40, Folder 74)
      One print has single typescript leaf (press release) attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: King-Weese Studios
    - Farkas, Francine (Box A-40, Folder 75)
    - Farley, Bettyann (Box A-40, Folder 76)
    - Farley, Charles M. (Box A-40, Folder 77)
    - Farmer, Alfonso (Box A-40, Folder 78)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International Photo
    - Farmer, Amara Kann (Box A-40, Folder 79)
    - Farmer, Art + Benny Golson (Jazztet) (Box A-40, Folder 80)
      Three prints have single typescript leaves attached.
      Photographer if identified: David Workman
      Number of Prints: 10
    - Farmer, Forest J. (Box A-40, Folder 81)
    - Farmer, Frederick (Patrolman) (Box A-40, Folder 82)
      Mounted on board.
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Studio
    - Farmer, James (Box A-40, Folder 83)
      One print has newspaper clipping adhered on verso; also one paper stereotype matrix and one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Frederick H. Simmons, James Gilbert, Sam Reiss, Cecil Layne, Alex Summers, Harris Photo, Anna Kaufman, Joe L. Perdue, Eli Aaron, David R. Holdrige
      Number of Prints: 25
    - Farmer, James (Mr. & Mrs) (Box A-40, Folder 84)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix.
    - Farmer, James Edward (V.P. Saturn Corp.) (Box A-40, Folder 85)
    - Farmer, Kathy (Box A-40, Folder 86)
    - Farmer, Richard (Box A-40, Folder 87)
    - Farmer, Shirley (Box A-40, Folder 88)
      One four-leaf typescript resume attached with staple in top left corner; one single-leaf typescript resume and one single-leaf typescript letter. Also one velox print mounted on paper.
    - Farmer, Shirley (Box A-40, Folder 89)
      One velox print with newspaper clipping attached.
    - Farr, Llewellyn (Box A-40, Folder 90)
    - Farr, Lorraine (Box A-40, Folder 91)
      Photographer if identified: Hayes Photo
    - Farr, Mel (Box A-40, Folder 92)
    - Farragut Tenant Association (Box A-40, Folder 93)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers
    - Farrakhan, Alpha (Box A-40, Folder 94)
    - Farrakhan (Box A-40, Folder 95)
      Also two velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Kenneth Mohammed, James Gilbert, Eric Ture Mohammed
    - Farrar, Joseph L. (Box A-40, Folder 96)
    - Farrar, James (Box A-40, Folder 97)
    - Farrar, Irene (Box A-40, Folder 98)
    - Farrel, Denny (Box A-40, Folder 99)
    - Farrell, Herman (Box A-40, Folder 100)
      One print has single typescript leaf attached with staple on border. Also one velox print with newspaper clipping attached.
      Photographer if identified: Monika Graff, Pictorial Enterprise, Carmen de Jesus, Monika Graff
      Number of Prints: 34
    - Farrell, Louis (Box A-40, Folder 101)
    - Farrell, Lyn (Box A-40, Folder 102)
    - Farrell, Sam (Box A-40, Folder 103)
      Single-leaf press release adhered on verso.
    - Farrell, Thomas (Box A-40, Folder 104)
      Photographer if identified: John Lowens
    - Farrer, Claire (Box A-40, Folder 105)
    - Farrington, John E. (Box A-40, Folder 106)
    - Farrington, Mary M. (Box A-40, Folder 107)
    - Farris, Alden Sgt. (Box A-40, Folder 108)
    - Farris, Christine K. (Mrs.) (Box A-40, Folder 109)
    - Farris, Cynthis (Box A-40, Folder 110)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo
    - Farris, Dionne (Box A-40, Folder 111)
    - Farris, John (Box A-40, Folder 112)
      Photographer if identified: Lloyd Yearwood
    - Farris, M.G. (Box A-40, Folder 113)
    - Farris, Vera (Dr.) (Box A-40, Folder 114)
    - Farris, Cynthia Belgrave (Box A-40, Folder 115)
    - Farwell, Mario (Box A-40, Folder 116)
    - Fascinations, The (Box A-40, Folder 117)
    - Fashaw, Jacqueline (Box A-40, Folder 118)
    - Fashion (Box A-40, Folder 119)
      Note on folder: "see Gwynne Tomlan." One print has single-leaf press release adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Coreen Simpson, Cleveland Davies, Pictorial Enterprise, Juanita M. Cole
      Number of Prints: 35
    - Fashion (Box OS-1, Folder 2)
    - Fashion + Industry H.S. (Box A-40, Folder 120)
    - Fashion & Jazz / '86 Fashion (Box A-40, Folder 121)
    - Fashionette Club (Box A-40, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: Alex Summers
    - Fashionettes (Box A-40, Folder 123)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers
    - Fat Albert (Box A-40, Folder 124)
    - Fasion, Ellen (Box A-40, Folder 125)
      See also "Ellen Faison."
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert
    - Fat Back Band (Box A-40, Folder 126)
      Photographer if identified: Bryan D. Hall
    - Fat, Syvilla (Box A-40, Folder 127)
      Photographer if identified: John Canada
    - Fat Tuesday (Box A-40, Folder 128)
    - Father's Day (Box A-40, Folder 129)
      Number of Prints: 8
    - Fatman, Deejay Lloyd (Box A-40, Folder 130)
    - Faucette, Maurice G. (Box A-40, Folder 131)
    - Faucette, Paul T. (Box A-40, Folder 132)
      Photographer if identified: Ray S. Brower Jr., Davidan Studios
      Number of Prints:
    - Faulding, Charles (Box A-40, Folder 133)
    - Faulding, Charles (Box A-40, Folder 134)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Images Unlimited, Jerry Soalt
    - Joe Faulk (Box A-40, Folder 135)
      Photographer if identified: Martine Barrat
    - Faulkner, Barbara N. (Box A-40, Folder 136)
    - Faulkner, Carlus E. (Box A-40, Folder 137)
      Newspaper clipping adhered on verso.
    - Faulkner, Geanie (Box A-40, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: Coreen Simpson
    - Faulkner, Gregory (Box A-40, Folder 139)
    - Faulkner, Harriet Y. (Box A-40, Folder 140)
    - Faulkner, Jeff (Box A-40, Folder 141)
    - Faxton, C. Figueroa (Box A-40, Folder 142)
    - Faulkner, Jeanne (Box A-40, Folder 143)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Norman Frederick
    - Faulkner, Wellington D. (Box A-40, Folder 144)
    - Fauntroy, Walter E. (Box A-40, Folder 145)
      Also one velox print and one program/pamphlet.
      Number of Prints: 11
    - Fauntleroy, Talmage R. (Box A-40, Folder 146)
    - Faust, Naomi (Dr.) (Box A-40, Folder 147)
    - Faust, Ray (Box A-40, Folder 148)
    - Fax, Elton C. (Box A-40, Folder 149)
      Also one velox print and one pencil drawing mounted on board.
      Photographer if identified: Whitestone Photo
    - Fay, Toni G. (Box A-40, Folder 150)
    - Faye, Toni (Box A-40, Folder 151)
    - Fayette County, Tennessee (Box A-40, Folder 152)
      Two typescript press releases (two leaves) attached with paperclip.
      Number of Prints: 19
    - Fayetteville State College (Box A-40, Folder 153)
      Sixteen prints have captions adhered with staples on border; two prints have typescript press releases attached with paperclip.
    - Fayetteville State College (Box A-40, Folder 154)
      One print has typescript press release attached with paperclip; nine have captions adhered with staples on border. One print mounted on paper with staples on border.
    - FDNY (Box A-40, Folder 155)
      Photo is torn/damaged.
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield
    - Fearing, Russell (Box A-40, Folder 156)
    - Feaster, Barbara (Box A-40, Folder 157)
    - Feaster, Norman & Tina (Box A-40, Folder 158)
    - Feaster, Patricia M. (Box A-40, Folder 159)
      Photographer if identified: Victor B. Greene
    - Feaster, Willie (Box A-40, Folder 160)
    - Featherson, Clarence H. (Box A-40, Folder 161)
    - Featherson, Clarence (Box A-40, Folder 162)
      Press release from Post Office Department attached with paperclip.
    - Featherston, Anthony (Box A-40, Folder 163)
      Print mounted on paper.
    - Featherston, Alfred D. (Box A-40, Folder 164)
    - Featherston, Dr. And Mrs. A. J. (Box A-40, Folder 165)
    - Featherston, Anthony G. (Box A-40, Folder 166)
    - Featherstone, Joanna (Box A-40, Folder 167)
    - Featherstone, Joanna (Box A-40, Folder 168)
    - Featherstone, Kevin (Box A-40, Folder 169)
    - Featherstone, Ralph (Box A-40, Folder 170)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos
    - FEDCO (Box A-40, Folder 171)
    - Federal City College (Box A-40, Folder 172)
      One print has press release attached with staple on border. Two other press releases attached to prints with paperclips. One print mounted on single-leaf press release.
      Photographer if identified: Leon M. Gurley
      Number of Prints: 6
    - Federal Highway Administration (Box A-40, Folder 173)
      Photographer if identified: Dept. Of Transportatation
    - Federated Clubs (Box A-40, Folder 174)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne
    - Federation of Negro Civil Service Org. (Box A-40, Folder 175)
      One print has single manuscript leaf attached with paperclip; one has newspaper clipping adhered on verso.
      Photographer if identified: David McAdams Photo, Curt Clemons,
    - Feddoes, Sadie (Box A-40, Folder 176)
      Also two velox prints. Two prints have staples on border.
      Photographer if identified: Neil De Angelis, King Photographers, Harris Photo, Norman Frederick, Pictorial Enterprise, Karl Crutchfield, Gene Tyler, Alex Summers,
      Number of Prints: 23
    - FEDS CBS (Box A-40, Folder 178)
    - Feed The Children (Box A-40, Folder 179)
    - Feelings, Tom (Box A-40, Folder 180)
    - Feggan, Ella (Mrs.) (Box A-40, Folder 181)
      Photographer if identified: Frederick H. Simmons
    - Feggans, Edward L. (Box A-40, Folder 182)
    - Fein, Danielle Webb (Box A-40, Folder 183)
    - Fela Anikulapo Kuti (Box A-40, Folder 184)
    - Fela, Orisa (Box A-40, Folder 185)
      Photographer if identified: Beifon
    - Feld, Rae (Mrs.) (Box A-40, Folder 186)
    - Felder, Cain (Box A-40, Folder 187)
      Photographer if identified: Paul Gentile
    - Felder, Quasar and Jack + Darren Canton (Box A-40, Folder 188)
    - Felder, Everett T. (Box A-40, Folder 189)
    - Felder, Harry (Box A-40, Folder 190)
    - Felder, Henry (Box A-40, Folder 191)
    - Felder, James L. (Box A-40, Folder 191a)
    - Feliciano, Jose (Box A-40, Folder 192)
    - Feliciano, Brenda (Box A-40, Folder 193)
    - Feliciano, Cheo (Box A-40, Folder 194)